<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Acid Chamber (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.AcidChamberDissolveAnything</packageId>
  <author>jspike</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/AcidChamberDissolveAnything</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies />
  <loadAfter />
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
Update of jspikes mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=824206983

- Should now be able to destroy all items as that seems to have been the intention of the mod
- Added support for [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2574489704]Simple FX: Smoke[/url]

Detailed description by user Thundercraft
[list]
[*]It runs on electricity, requiring 250w (the same as the Crematorium it resembles).
[*]It has a cleanliness value of -20, just like a Crematorium.
[*]The research cost is 750, the tech level is Industrial and the prerequisite is Electricity.
[*]Building it costs 150 stone, 50 Steel and 5 Components, which is more than twice the Steel and Components of a Crematorium.
[*]This Acid Chamber actually produces about 25% more heat than a Crematorium.
[*]A Crematorium has -10 Beauty, but this Acid Chamber does not.
[/list]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/pufA0kM.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/AcidChamberDissolveAnything][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/WjDSfUn.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/h5VwTNL.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z4GOv8H.png[/img]
Chamber full of acid designed to dissolve any item in a matter of minutes. Bulk(20x) option included as well. Works similar to the cremation chamber but for any in game item. Puts off a cancer causing green glow and leaks acid but it gets the job done. Even fits nicely into the Research tab.

Originally created for myself but figured some others might be interested. Please comment if you find bugs or whatever. I'm running a ton of mods and haven't had any problems yet. 

Supports v.16

[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]

</description>
</ModMetaData>